(Yin Jisheng)
(Zheng Liyu)
"Thunderstorm"
Am I ugly now?
Not very ugly
It hurts, right?
It won't hurt if you apply medicine on me
There is no such thing
I mean it
Stop putting medicine on me and kiss me
Oh, the medicine has just been applied.
Angry
where are you going
go to sleep
Won't you accompany me?
I can't bear it
Then don't bear it
Don't
I want to cherish you
so suddenly
Yeah
No one can treat you casually
I can't let you get hurt either
you can treat me whatever you want
You will sleep in my room from now on
Are you going to leave my room alone and not sleep?
If you want to continue living in my house, just do as I say.
Otherwise...
What would happen otherwise
Don't know
Let's sleep together in my room today
whatever you want
One photo
sorry
Did it bother you?
You don't need to clean anymore from now on
I will find the cleaning lady again
why
This will make you tired
You go wash up and change clothes first.
Waiting to go out
are we going out
Yeah
Is there nothing you want to do?
I want to stay at home
Hello
What's wrong
Is it reasonable?
The weather is so nice, you actually want to stay at home
I will stay at home tomorrow, the day after tomorrow, and the day after tomorrow.
Why do you still want to stay at home?
Forget it
OK
Let's get out quickly
ok
Let's go
Very ordinary
Special items
Exchange for another piece
Quite cute
Do you want to choose this one?
please give me this
Is it delicious?
Yeah, delicious
Alas
Why do you eat until your mouth is full?
I wipe it myself
ok
So good
what are you doing
very hot
Zhenghan, let me go to the toilet.
Zhenghan
What are you doing?
why are you like this
let go
Do I make you shy?
No
Do I embarrass you?
Yeah, you wouldn't think so
this is our first time
first date outside
sorry
But I don't want this
I don’t want you to be troubled because of me
If someone else sees it...
So you said you wanted to stay at home because...
I'm really going to be driven crazy by you
Hey, what are you doing?
Come up
Give you 10 seconds
10 9 8…
3 2 1…
Hurry up
Don't fall
sorry
are you sad
Yeah
Did you work so hard when you liked me?
There are more happy days than hard times
Alas, I realized there is a flaw when I carry you on my back
what
I want to kiss you right away but I can’t
One photo
Yeah
Do you still like me?
What's the answer?
You don't answer anything
I said let’s fall in love
Miss me and you will regret it
let me go
I'll wait for you to answer before letting you go.
Do you think you can ever meet someone as handsome as me?
People can't just look at faces
I won't let you suffer
I will always carry you
but i like walking
Then I will let you live in my house for the rest of your life
no...wrong
Or should I give you that house?
Zhenghan: People's hearts cannot be bought with money.
Hello Li Yizhao
I will regret missing you
I know it's a bit late
But can you give me a chance...
please
Go in
At least tell me the reason
ok
Let's fall in love
But
you have to promise me something
what
-If we cause harm to each other, do we need to break up?
Yeah
I don't want to be with you with a hurt heart
good
I won't hurt you
But I also have a request
what
Don't just disappear without saying anything.
Don't do this again
Yeah
One photo
What kind of person were you dating before?
Just an ordinary person
Did he write to you?
Yeah
-Are you handsome? -Yeah
Hello
you are more handsome
Don't you have any photos of your ex?
No
How is it possible
bring the phone over
What are you doing?
Because I want to confirm whether I am the most handsome one
I just said you are the most handsome
That's why I asked you to show me
No
why not
Those people are all passers-by anyway.
One photo
are you asleep
Let's get off the car together
I'll get off first
Look at the road
-Hello -Hello
hello good morning
-Hi, good morning. -Hello.
Are you weirder now?
I'm leaving
One photo
It's Zhenghan
Do you come to work together?
-Yes -I...
we live together
what
It turns out you are very familiar with each other. What is your relationship?
- We... - We're cousins.
Yes we are cousins
Oh my God, no wonder
You two are very handsome
I still have to go to work. Let’s go in first.
- Come on - Come on
Why didn't you tell us?
I'm so envious that you guys actually live together.
Envy? Who do you envy?
Ah, by the way
Does Yizhao have a date?
Yes
His partner is a cool guy
What about you?
I have it too
I really envy the two of you.
Right
Wait
Wow really
-It must be very painful, right? -Yes.
good morning
Zhenghan
Xu Zhenghan, it seems there is something good going on.
He said he was in love
Now is the age to make a splash
Okay, go and do your work
Then I'll take my leave first.
All my colleagues in the company know that I am in love
did you really say that
Three cups of Americano coffee and two cups of ice tea
I heard you are in love
I heard your partner is cool
Yes
14,400 won
today
my treat
Like
-Then let's find a seat first. -Okay
Let's go
Hello
What's wrong with you?
This is very exciting
I'll come down after work later
I'll wait for you in the parking lot
Why doesn't he come out yet?
You haven't wiped it there yet. Please wipe it clean for me.
You didn't mop it up, okay?
What nonsense are you talking about? Your fingerprints are all here.
-Don't make trouble. -Then just wipe it properly.
Zhenghan
hello
Don't make trouble
what's the matter with you
Let working-study students get off work on time
I want to get off work with him
Hello
Let's go, take a photo
wait for me
Zhenghan
What are you doing?
Are you uncomfortable?
No one has any other ideas
Not like that
Let's go. Thank you for your hard work.
you see
They don't care at all
Yeah
I'm going to have dinner with Xiuxiao today
why
Just... friends
You…
I know
Are you okay?
Yeah
I'm very generous when I'm in love
I know
Please contact me again
-I'll pick you up. -No, don't make it such a hassle.
You go home first
Okay, then I'll go to sleep first
Li Yizhao, are you really...
have you been here
No. Where are you?
I was here last time
The atmosphere here is great and the food is delicious
what do you want to eat
I can eat anything
when did you come
About a month ago
Who did you come with?
Just with friends
Do you want some soju?
But the atmosphere here is great
Not bad
I just want to come and eat with you
How are you doing lately?
That's it
Are you still living at his house?
Yeah
I think you should move out as soon as possible. Are you okay?
The money I earn from working now is not enough to pay the rent.
So do you want to switch to full-time work?
Otherwise, I would come to work on weekends too.
Really?
Well, I will help you arrange it.
Got it, I'll consider it
Right
Save your money quickly and move out from there
I can't stand that guy. He seems to think you're easy to handle.
Why did you call him 'that guy'?
Does he treat others as playthings?
Actually
we are dating
what
When did it start?
not long yet
Sorry I didn't tell you in advance
Hey, what do you have to apologize for?
So, are you happy?
Don't you like that guy?
happy
I don't want to say that either
But I'm a little worried about you
One look and I know that only you will be hurt
It doesn't matter
But I'm still very happy
Hello Li Yizhao
Be careful
Maybe the two of them colluded.
-Blood relations cannot be deceived... -Xiu Xiao
let's go out
It's not even 10 o'clock yet
Because Zhenghan is waiting for me
Hello Li Yizhao
you really are...
sorry
Let's go
I want to checkout
The total is 67,000 won
-Thank you. -Good job.
Repair effect I am very full
Zhenghan
Why are you here...
Oh Li Yizhao
Do you still smoke?
Why hide it?
I haven't hidden anything
You never asked me
Have you finished eating with that guy?
What is 'that guy'?
You two are really...
How
Did that guy call me 'that guy' too?
Say no more
what did you talk about
secret
why come here
What...
what are you doing
come here
what
I asked you to come over to the driver's seat
I will reward you
Wait...
be careful
If the horn is sounded, all residents in the neighborhood will be woken up.
How about I take off my shirt?
But today, it looks like I didn’t come to work.
I heard that he didn't come to work because he went to the hospital.
So today the cafe manager also postponed the opening of the store
Is the photo showing someone being beaten?
Looks like long term violent injury
Li Yizhao
what's going on
Zhenghan, I will explain to you
What the hell is going on